Guide to the Duke University Libraries Collection of Haggadot, 1200-2003 (bulk1900-2003)
Duke University Libraries Collection of Haggadot 1200-2003 (bulk 1900-2003
- Purpose List Series, 1200-2003
  - Facsimile Subseries, 1200-1990, (34 items)
    - Hagadah shel Pesah / [`orekh u-mehkar, Nahman Ran, `orekhet mishneh, Nivah Penai] = Passover Haggadah / [editor and research, Nachman Ran, assist. editor, Niva Panai], 1751., 28 x 329 cmfolded to 28 x 12 cm. Illustrated.
      Facsimile was published in Tel Aviv, 1986. Facsimile of: The Altona-Hamburg Haggadah. Manuscript. 1751 (Codex Levy 22). English and Hebrew. Map of the Land of Israel, drawn by Abraham Bar-Yaacov, the first Hebrew-letter printed map, attached to the Amsterdam Haggadah from 1696--P. [27-30] By the Scriber ... Uri Feivisch, son of Rabbi Itzhak Eizik ....
    - Hagadah shel Pesah / [`orekh u-mehkar, Nahman Ran, `orekhet mishneh, Nivah Penai] = Passover Haggadah / [editor and research, Nachman Ran, assist. editor, Niva Panai], 1751., 28 x 329 cmfolded to 28 x 12 cm. Illustrated.
    - Passover Haggada: Germany, 1768 / scribe/illustrator, Nathan ben Abraham Speyer of Breslau; collection of the Jewish National and University Library, Jerusalem, Ms. Heb. 8vo 2340 = Hagadah shel Pesah: Ashkenaz, 528 (1768) / katav ve-tsiyer Natan ben Avraham Shpaiyer mi-Bresla; osef Bet ha-sefarim ha-le'umi veha-universita'i, Yerushalayim, ketav-yad 8vo 2340, 1768., 30 cm. Illuminated.
      Facsimile was published in Tel Aviv, 1984. Text in Hebrew, rubrics in Yiddish. Accompanied by introductory material in Hebrew and English, including bibliographies, prepared by Chaya Benjamin.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: Tri'esti 624 = The Passover Haggadah: Trieste 1864 / mahadurat Avraham Hai Morpurgo; ha-ilustratsyot `a. y. K. Krikhmayer [sic], 1864., 32 cm. Illustrated.
      Facsimile was printed in Jerusalem in 1974.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Pessah Hagada, 1951-1952., 42 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Facsim. of: Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: bi-leshon ha-kodesh u-fitrono bi-leshon Ashkenazim ... Venitsiyah: Stamperia Vendramina, 501 [1740 or 1741] This Hagada -- printed in Jerusalem by Hamadpis Lipshitz Press, is a reproduction of an old Venetian edition of which the above [as in Facsim. note] is the original title page. It contained an Italian [?] translation, for which English has been substituted--Colophon. Ha-tseva`im veha-tsiurim ve-seder ha-`amudim hut`amu le-tavnit ha-hotsa'at--Colophon. `Al ha-kerikhah tsiur Ha lahma `anya bi-tseva`im mi-tokh Hagadat Sarayevo--Yaari. Yaari 2416
    - Hagadah shel Pesah / he`etik u-tsayar Benyamin Sha'n; `im targum, mavo, u-he'arot me-et Betsalel Rot, 1966., 40 cm.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah nikhtevah ve-tsuyerah be-Nikelsburg bi- shenat 508 = The Passover Haggadah written and illustrated in Nickelsburg 1748, 1973., 30 cm. Illustrated.
    - Passover Hagadah / illustrated with the commentary of Rabbi Dr. Marcus Lehmann of Mainz, rendered into English for the first time, 1975., 26 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah le-zekher ha-Sho`ah = Pessach Haggadah in memory of the Holocaust / illustrated by David Wander; calligraphy and micrography by Yonah Weinrib, 1985., 43 cm. Illustrated.
    - A song of David: a limited edition facsimile of the Moss Haggadah / [David Moss], 1987., 46 cm. Illuminated.
      Hebrew text; companion volume about the Moss Haggadah is in Hebrew and English. Artistically it includes: calligraphy, micrography, gouaches, gold leaf, acrylics and paper cuts. Moss reproduces the crafts and style of the medieval scribe with modern innovation designed to bring the story of the Exodus up to the present time and to connect it to present-day Jews and to the founding of the state of Israel.
    - The tree [picture], 1987., 49 x 34 cm. Illustrated.
      Page from the the Moss Haggadah, by David Moss. This page contains in its micrographic border, the entire text of the Haggadah in Hebrew. Duke also owns two versions of the complete Moss Haggadah: Haggadah f#12 and Haggadah f#26.
    - €˜Arba` hagadot = 4 haggadot: me-'osef Bet ha-sefarim ha-le'umi veha-universita'i bi-Yerushalayim, 1989., 26 x 37 x 3 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Moss Haggadah: a complete reproduction of the Haggadah written and illuminated by David Moss for Richard and Beatrice Levy, with the commentary of the artist, 1990., 36 cm. Illustrated.
      Haggadah text in Hebrew; commentary in English. Accompanied by: The Passover Haggadah: an English translation to accompany the Moss Haggadah; and a paper-cut print of The bird cage from the original work.
  - Fundraising Subseries, 1937-1979, (45 items)
    Printed and distributed in an effort to raise money for various organizations. Generally contain the traditional text and may have illustrations by well-known artists or be reproductions of early manuscripts. Always include a letter thanking the reader for, or requesting, donations. Duke University Libraries' earliest fundraising Haggadah was printed in 1937 by the Pro-Palestine Fund in its efforts to raise money for the Jewish pioneers who were living in Palestine (Haggadah Pam 12mo #34).
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Passover Hagadah: services for the Passover nights / arranged by H. Meiliz; with illustrations, 1937., 18 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 1943., 14 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Hagadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Nota Koslowsky, 1944., 14 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Hagadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Nota Koslowsky, 1944., 14 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: matanah me-et Yeshivah u-Metivta Rabenu Shelomoh Kluger, z.ts.l., 376 Ist Hoysten Strit, Nyu York = Souvenir of the Yeshiva and Mesifta Rabbi Solomon Kluger, 376 East Houston Street, New York, 1944., 18 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1949., 15 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1949., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Passover Haggadah / with a new translation by Saadyah Maximon; and illustrations by Paul K. Freeman, 1949-1950., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1951., 14 cm. Illustrated.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah] = The haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1951., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Passover Haggadah / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1953., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Passover Haggadah / a faithful English rendering by A. Regelson; illustrations by S. Forst, 1959., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - The book of Passover; Passover in life and literature and Haggadah, 195-?., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Passover Haggadah = [Hagadah shel Pesah] / with a new translation by Saadyah Maximon and illustrations by Paul K. Freeman, 1960., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Passover Haggadah = [Hagadah shel Pesah] / with a new translation by Saadyah Maximon and illustrations by Paul K. Freeman, 1960., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Passover Haggadah / with a new translation by Saadyah Maximon; and illustrations by Paul K. Freeman, 1960., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - The first known printed Passover Hagadah / by Gershom Kohen, 1960., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah] = From twilight to dawn, the traditional Pessach Hagadah / arranged by Rabbi Shlomo Kahn, 1960., 24 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: first printed edition of a Haggadah from a parchment manuscript of the early eighteenth Century, anno 1731, Hamburg ... / courtesy of New York Public library - Jewish Division, 1961., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: ketav-yad me-osef Baron David Gintsburg ha-nimtsa be-Sifriyah ha-le'umit be-Moskva = The Günzburg Haggadah: first printed edition of an illuminated manuscript from the USSR microfilm collection in the New York University Library of Judaica and Hebraica, 1962., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Cecil Roth Oxford Haggadah: written in 1753 and subsequently owned by Joseph b. Leizer Speier of Amsterdam., 1963., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Pessach Haggadah = Hagadah shel Pesah, 1964., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: ketav yad metsuyar `al Klaf me-Osef Sifriyat Bet ha-nivharim be-Vashington mi-shenat...1470 = The Washington Haggadah: first printed edition of an illuminated manuscript from the Library of Congress.., 1965., 14 x 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Passover Haggadah = [Hagadah shel Pesah]: a faithful English rendering / by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1966., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah mi-tokh mahazor Roma = The Mahzor Roma Haggadah: Bologna, Italy, anno 1540 / from the copy at the New York Public Library, Jewish Division, 1966., 22 cm. Text only.
    - [Hagadat Yehude Sin] = The Haggadah of the Chinese Jews: first printed edition from a manuscript of the seventeenth-eighteenth Century C.E. originating in the Jewish colony of K'ai-Feng Fu / with an introduction by Prof. Cecil Roth, 1967., 22 cm. Text only.
    - [Hagadat Yehude Sin] = The Haggadah of the Chinese Jews: first printed edition from a manuscript of the seventeenth-eighteenth Century C.E. originating in the Jewish colony of K'ai-Feng Fu / with an introduction by Prof. Cecil Roth, 1967., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadat Bene Yisra'el = The Haggadah of the Bene Israel of India, 1968., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Passover Haggadah / illustrated by children of the arts and crafts classes of the General Israel Orphan's Home in Jerusalem; with a guide for the Seder, 196-?., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Tel Aviv Haggadah: first printed edition of an 18th Century illuminated handwritten Haggadah with an abridged version of Don Isaac Abarbanel's Commentary, 1771 .., 1971., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Tel Aviv Haggadah: first printed edition of an 18th Century illuminated handwritten Haggadah with an abridged version of Don Isaac Abarbanel's Commentary, 1771 .., 1971., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Tel Aviv Haggadah: first printed edition of an 18th Century illuminated handwritten Haggadah with an abridged version of Don Isaac Abarbanel's Commentary, 1771 .., 1971., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah bi-leshon ha-kodesh u-fitrono bi-leshon Italyano = The Venice Haggadah with Judeo-Italian translation, Venice 1609, 1973., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Let my people go: a Haggadah / Illustrated by Mark Podwal. Foreword by Abba Eban. Introd. by Theodore Bikel, 1973., 29 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Kittsee Haggadah: first printed edition of an 18th Century illuminated handwritten Haggadah, 1782 .., 1975., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah seder shel Pesah = The Fuerth haggadah, 1976., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Leipnik-Rosenthaliana Haggadah, 1977., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Vienna Haggadah, 1978., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder ha-Hagadah shel Pesah: `im tsiyurim = The Trieste Haggadah of 1864 / hugah be-`iyun ... me-et Avraham Hai Morpurgo; [with introduction by Tovia Preschel; pref. by Munish Weintraub], 1979., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - [Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im perush yafeh ve-tsiyurim na'i. meha-otot veha-moftim she-`asah ha-K. b.h. la-avotenu] = The Hamburg-Amsterdam Haggadah of 1728, 1980., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah ... = the Hamburg-Amsterdam Haggadah of 1728, 1980., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Amsterdam Haggadah of 1662, 1981., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Amsterdam Haggadah of 1662, 1981., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: bi-leshon ha-kodesh uvi-leshon Italyano = The Venice Haggadah, 1716: with Judeo-Italian translation, 1991., 22 cm. Illustrated.
  - General Subseries, 1526-2003, (215 items)
    For use at a Passover seder. Typically traditional in content, come in a variety of languages, and include both illustrated and non-illustrated examples.
    - Die Pessach-Haggadah des Gerschom Kohen, 1527 [i.e. 1526], 1526., 32 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah bi-leshon ha-kodesh uvi-leshon Italyano: `im kamah tsurot `al kol ha-otot veha-moftim asher na`asu la-avotenu be-Mitsrayim, ba-yam uva-midbar ... / ve-gam ba be-tokham pe. Tseli esh ... ve-hu kitsur Zevah Pesah m.h. Rav Don Yitshak Abravan[el] z.l, 1715-1716., 32 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: im birkhoteha, 1728-1729., 15 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah Seder shel Pesah, 1740-1741., 31 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagada le-Fesah, 1764-1765., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1779-1780., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Helek rishon mi-Sefer arba' yesodot, 1782-1783., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah Seder shel Pesah, 1782-1783., 31 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1795-1796., 17 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel pesah: ins daytsh, iberzetst und mit nittslikhen anmerkungn ferzehn, 1795., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Compendium orationum = [Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: kefi minhag Ashkenazim] .., 1828., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, oder, Fortrag oyf dia beyden erzten abende Pesah, 1829., 17 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = Service for the two first nights of Passover: in Hebrew and English, according to the custom of the German and Polish Jews / carefully revised and corrected by Isaac Levi .., 1842., 21 cm. Illuminated.
    - Hagadah = Racconto degli avvenimenti memorabili occasionanti la Pasqua / traduzione riveduta e corretta dall' Mayer Randegger, 1851., 21 cm. Text only.
      Contains traditional Hebrew text with an Italian translation. Handwritten notes appear throughout in Hebrew (Rashi script), Italian, and Greek Four handwritten pages, In Hebrew and Italian, were inserted into the beginning of the Haggadah. These pages serve as an annotated table of contents. Signed on the inside of the cover.
    - Sefer Pi ha-medaber: (notarikon perush Hagadah / mi-meni Yosef bar Rabenu David), 1853-1854., 25 cm. Text only.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah: `im ha`atakah u-hora'at ha-dinim u-ha-minhagim ba-lashon hollandit] = Hagadah, voordragt op de beide eerste avonden van het Paasch-feest: in het Nederduitsch vertaald en met vele ophelderingen voorzien / door G.A. Parser .., 1864., 17 cm. Text only.
    - Sefer zikrono le-hayyim: le-zikaron ka'iti ha-nes le-mino be-mile de-Agadata lel hitkadesh hag ha-Pesah ... / ve-hu ha-tsa'ir Hayyim ha-kohen .., 1874-1875., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1868., 23 cm. Text only.
    - [Hagadah ve-seder shel Pesah] = Form of service for the two first nights of the feast of Passover, 1869., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah] = Hagadah, voordragt op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met aanwijzing der gebruiken in het Nederduitsch, 1876., 18 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Ha-Hagadah le-lel shemorim: meduyak hetiv u-mesudar yafe u-meturgam ashkenazit = Hagadah / me-et Volf ben Shimshon ben ish Haidenhaim, 1877., 18 cm.
    - Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah = Hagadah, voordragt op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met Nederduitsche opschriften, 1884., 19 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah ve-seder shel Pesah = Form of service for the first two nights of the feast of Passover / with English translation, 1886., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im tsiurim ve-targum `Aravi: ke-minhag k.k. Bagaad: ... ve-`atah hosafnu vo piyutim nehmadim, tefilat `arvit ... ve-dinim ha-nitsrakhim .., 1886-87., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer Hakam lev / notri. leha-tsa`ir Kamos ben Musa Had'ad, 1886-87., 29 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1893., 20 cm. Text only.
    - The Haggadah according to the rite of Yemen: together with the Arabic-Hebrew commentary / published for the first time from mss. of Yemen with an introduction, translation and critical and philological notes by William H. Greenburg, 1896., 23 cm. Text only.
    - The Haggadah according to the rite of Yemen: together with the Arabic-Hebrew commentary / published for the first time from mss. of Yemen with an introduction, translation and critical and philological notes by William H. Greenburg, 1896., 23 cm. Text only.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah] = Voordracht op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met Nederlandsche opschriften, 1897., 19 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1897., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1889-1890., 18 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer Magid mesharim: hu be'ur hadash u-maspik `al Hagadah shel Pesah: `im mavo gadol ... me-eti Netan'el Hayyim b. Mosheh Naman Pape, 1899-1900., 24 cm. Text only.
    - The Erna Michael wood blocks; twenty nine illustrations from original wood blocks successors of the Venice Haggadah. Introduction by Bezalel Narkiss, 19th Century., 33 cm. Illustrated.
      Not a Haggadah, as it does not contain any text. This is, however, a collection of 29 imprints made in 1977 from original 19th Century wood blocks based on the famous Venice Haggadah of 1609. The near completeness of the collection of biblical and ritual wood cuts intended for printing is a rare find.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = Hagada: Gebete für den häuslichen Gottesdienst am ersten und zweiten Abende des Pessachfestes / Deutsch übersetzt und erlautert von Dr. R.T. Fürstenthal; nebst einem Gedichte "Das Pessachfest" von Salomon Plessner, 1900., 18 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1904., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: `im perush uminhage ... M.h.R.L. mi-Prag, 1905., 24 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im matayim sheloshim u-shemoneh perushim ve-hosafot / me-et maranan ve-rabanan geonim kedoshim .., 1907., 22 cm. Text only.
    - [Seder ha-Hagadah le-lele Pesah] = Hagadah, voordracht op de beide eerste avonden van het Pesach-feest: met Nederlandsche opschriften, 1909., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Seder ha-Hagadah le-lel shimurim = Erzählung von dem Auszuge Israels aus „gypten... / übersetzt von W. Heidenheim .., 190-?., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: een verzameling van gebeden, vertellingen en liederen, ten gebruike voor de Pesach-avondviering: zoowel in huiselijken kring als in gezamenlijke bijeenkomsten, 190-?., 20 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Hagadah for Passover: with English translation, 1901-1902., 16 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: leshon ... `aravi menukad ke-fi minhag ... Bagdad ... ve-gam ke-fi `are Hodu: ve-nosaf `od meturgemet bi-leshon Anglizi, .., 1903-1904., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im pitaron be-lashon Italiki `im kamah tsurot ... ve-nosaf ... tefilat `Arvit .., 1903-1904., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im be'ur hadash Tavlin le- mitsvah ...: ha-nushah ha-nehugah ule-`umatah nushat ha-Rambam / yatsa le-or `al yede Avraham Aharon ha-Levi Prag, 1909-1910., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1910., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah le-lel shemurim: meduyak hetiv, mesudar yafeh u-meturgam anglit = Service for the first two nights of Passover, 1912., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = Form of services for the first two nights of Passover, with illustrations / revised and edited by A. Th. Philips, 1912., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder hagadah shel Pesah = form of services for the first two nights of Passover, with illustrations / revised and edited by Dr. A. Th. Philips, music by H. A. Russoto, 1912., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: mit zekhzig perushim in `ivri taitsh, 1912., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah mit myuzik noten = Passover Hagadah with music, 1912?., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah le-lel shimurim: `im be'ur Masa ge ha-hizayon ... / hiber ... Aryeh Leb Frumkin .., 1912-1913., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: iberzetst idish mit talmudishe legenden wegen yetsi'at Mitsraim: mit fiel biblishe bilder / bearbaitet durkh H. Niselavits, 1913-1914., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im ha`atakah `ivri taitsh ha-meduveret benenu ve-`im perush u-meshalim meha-Rav ha-m.m. mi-Dubna: `im shev`ah tsiurim yafim ve-na`im, 1916., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah = The Seder service for the first two nights of Passover, with illustrations / revised and edited by Herman Klopper; music composed, selected and arranged by Henry A. Russoto, 191-?., 18 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: ...mit sipurim oyf `Ivri Taytsh, 1921., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hebrew title romanized. | Cover title: Hagadah shel Pesah = Hagadah for Passover, 1921., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Edited and printed by "Union" (Appel Brothers)
    - Hagadah shel Pesah be-'otiyot gedolot u-vehirot: mit di dinim vas zainen shaiakh tsu bedikat homets un di sedarim in Idish .., 1921., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder ha-Hagadah le-lel shimurim = Erzählung von dem Auszuge Israels aus „gypten für die beiden ersten Pessachabende / nach W. Heidenheim; neu übersetzt von Rabbiner Dr. Selig Bamberger, 1921., 25 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Seder service Hagadah for Passover / ... meturgam `al yede Rahel Me'ir .., 1922., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1922., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagada: aangeboden door de firma Wed. J. Stein, Amsterdam .., 1922., 23 cm. Text only.
    - The Union Haggadah: home service for the Passover / [edited by the Central Conference of American Rabbis], 1923., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Haggadah shel Pesah, 1923., 27 cm. Illustrated.
    - Haggada de Pessah / texte hébreu revu par le rabbin Back; mis en français par Edmond Fleg; orné d'illustrations de Janine Aghion, 1925., 28 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1926., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder hagadah le-lele Pesah: `im ezeh devarim al mekorah mi-kunteres magid me-reshit le-d.a. landshuteh, ve-`im hora'at ha-dinim veha-minhagim be-lashon hollandit = Voordracht voor de beide eerste avonden van het Paaschfeest: met aanwijzing der voorschriften en gebruiken in de nederlandsche taal / door G.I. Polak, 1926., 19 cm. Text only.
    - Sefer Navah tehilah `al Hagadah shel Pesah / ... amarim ... mi-tokh kitve ... Ya`akov David ... me-Radomsk; divre ha-mesader ... Noah Vayntrob, 1926-1927., 21 cm. Text only.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1927., 22 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah `im tsiyurim = Hagadah / arranged by J. D. Eisenstein; illustrated by Lola, 1928., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1928., 19 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pessah': (ritual da ceia Pascal) / traduçao e arranjo de A.C. de Barros Basto (Ben-Rosh), 1928., 19 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah., 192-?., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1930., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1930., 32 cm. Illustrated.
    - The Haggadah: a new edition / with English translation, introduction, and notes by Cecil Roth; with drawings by Donia Nachshen, 1934., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah le-Pesah nusah ha-Rambam be-sifro ha-Yad ha-hazakah ...: `im biografiah ketsarah me-hayey ha-Rambam ... :`a.p. seder minhage ha-Gra mi-Vilna .., 1935., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah le-Bet Ya`akov: `ivrit ve-'idit `im sipurim ve-perushim migdole ha-darshanim u-venam R. Ya`akov mi-Dubna, 1935., 17 cm. Text only.